

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABDULAKHAD TURGUNALIEV

CONTANCTS

Uzbek: +998 (90) 111 65 54 Gmail: iamabdulakhad@gmail.com
Poland: +48 789 612 281 Telegram: @Hammasi_Ota_Onam_Sababli

Świętego Bonifacego 77, Warsaw, Poland

ABOUT ME

An accomplished and diligent FRONT–END Developer with a practical experience of more than 2 years in programming.

Seeking a challenging position as a FRONT–END Developer in an organization where I can utilize my qualification in programming to contribute to the triumph of the company.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Practical experience with SQL
- Projects with Javascript, React Js and Three.js
- IT systems management
- · Basics of Python and C#
- Website development
- · Mathematics and statistics

SOFT SKILLS

- Eloquence
- Communication
- Leadership
- Punctual
- Multitasking
- Creativity

HARD SKILLS

- Proficient in all Microsoft Office Suite
- Task-oriented
- IELTS(7.5)
- Critical thinking
- Decision-making
- Problem-solving
- Persuasion

LANGUAGE

- English(C1)
- Russian (advanced)
- · Uzbek(native)

EXPERIENCE

26.06.2023-06.10.2023

"FOREIGN LANGUAGE" TV CHANNEL

FRONTMAN IN " FOREIGN LANGUAGE" TV PROGRAM - UZBEKISTAN

- Writing scenario for IT Lesson, which would be transmitted during the live broadcast, to instructing students willing to learn programming for free throughout the TV.
- Arranging sequence of pages and turn of hostmans during the lesson and on-time illustration of photos and slides needed for lesson.
- · Interviewing candidates for hosting IT Lesson in order to make verify their knowledge of programming.

20.06.2023 - 25.09.2023

"MARS" IT SCHOOL

SUPPORT MENTOR IN " MARS" IT SCHOOL - UZBEKISTAN

- Instructing students below the high school age rudiments of Javascript, even teaching complex topics in their own language.
- Editing video and photo slides or even creating short–lasting cartoons for kids, as animation and illustration is the most ultimate way of teaching juveniles.
- Organizing weekly exams, hold as a competition for an hour individuallesson, to verify progress and actual knowledge of young and prosperous children.

29.07.2023 - 05.10.2023

"WEB-BRAIN ACADEMY" IT SCHOOL

MENTOR IN "WEB-BRAIN ACADEMY" IT SCHOOL

- Instructing students above the high school age HTML, CSS, Javascript and React Js courses whether
 online or offline, according to the courses they enrolled in.
- Freeing adamant and ignorant students, determined by the test after terminating any programming language, who can not keep up the pace that others have.
- Organizing Live Zoom Tutorials for students to re-explain topics that are hard to absorb at once and takes time to be embedded deeply into mind.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING IN ACADEMY OF FINANCE AND BUSINESS VISTULA UNIVERSITY

OCTOBER 2023 - PRESENT

WEB-BRAIN ACADEMY IT SCHOOL CERTIFICATE OF SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETION OF FRONT-END DEVELOPING. 09.01.2023-27.08.2023